A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Log Files (Grant and Project Proposals) FA734
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1957-1976
  - L65-269 to L65-343, 1965 (Reel L-217)
  - L65-344 to L65-393, 1965 (Reel L-218)
  - L65-395 to L65-502, 1965 (Reel L-219)
  - L65-506 to L65-547, 1965 (Reel L-220)
  - L65-548 to L65-600, 1965 (Reel L-221)
  - L65-602 to L65-626, 1965 (Reel L-222)
  - L66-2 to L66-30, 1966 (Reel L-223)
  - L66-31 to L66-85, 1966 (Reel L-224)
  - L66-87 to L66-114 (continued on reel #L-226), 1966 (Reel L-225)
  - L66-114 to L66-137, 1966 (Reel L-226)
  - L66-139 to L66-166 (continued on reel #L-228), 1966 (Reel L-227)
  - L66-166 to L66-176, 1966 (Reel L-228)
  - L66-177 to L66-210, 1966 (Reel L-229)
  - L66-211 to L66-253 (continued on reel #L-231), 1966 (Reel L-230)
  - L66-253 to L66-287, 1966 (Reel L-231)
  - L66-288 to L66-336, 1966 (Reel L-232)
  - L66-317 to L66-324, 1966 (Reel L-233)
  - L66-337 to L66-389, 1966 (Reel L-234)
  - L66-390 to L66-416 (continued on reel #L-237), 1966 (Reel L-235)
  - L66-436, 1966 (Reel L-236)
  - L66-416 to L66-475, 1966 (Reel L-237)
  - (L66-436 is housed on reel #L-236, L66-445 is housed on reel #L-240)
  - L66-476 to L66-530, 1966 (Reel L-238)
  - L66-532 to L66-586, 1966 (Reel L-239)
  - L66-587 to L66-618, L66-445, 1966 (Reel L-240)
  - L67-2 to L67-70, 1967 (Reel L-241)
  - L67-71 to L67-128, 1967 (Reel L-242)
  - L67-130 to L67-179, 1967 (Reel L-243)
  - L67-179 to L67-211, 1967 (Reel L-244)
  - L67-212 to L67-252 (continued on reel #L-246), 1967 (Reel L-245)
  - L67-252 to L67-297 (continued on reel #L-247), 1967 (Reel L-246)
  - L67-297 to L67-342, 1967 (Reel L-247)
  - L67-343 to L67-387, 1967 (Reel L-248)
  - L67-388 to L67-424 (continued on reel #L-250), 1967 (Reel L-249)
  - L67-424 to L67-463 (continued on reel #L-251), 1967 (Reel L-250)
  - L67-463 to L67-486 (continued on reel #L-252), 1967 (Reel L-251)
  - L67-486 to L67-499, 1967 (Reel L-252)
  - L67-500 to L67-515, 1967 (Reel L-253)
  - L67-516 to L67-584, 1967 (Reel L-254)
  - L67-585 to L67-627, 1967 (Reel L-255)
  - L67-630 to L67-669, 1967 (Reel L-256)
  - L68-8 to L68-48, 1968 (Reel L-257)
  - L68-49 to L68-55, 1968 (Reel L-258)
  - L68-56 to L68-60, 1968 (Reel L-259)
  - L68-61 to L68-76, 1968 (Reel L-260)
  - L68-77 to L68-93, 1968 (Reel L-261)
  - L68-95 toL68-104, 1968 (Reel L-262)
  - L68-106 to L68-150, 1968 (Reel L-263)
  - L68-151 to L68-182, 1968 (Reel L-264)
  - L68-184 to L68-215 (continued on reel #L-266), 1968 (Reel L-265)
  - L68-215 to L68-231, 1968 (Reel L-266)
  - L68-237 to L68-303 (continued on reel #L-268), 1968 (Reel L-267)
  - L68-303 to L68-322, 1968 (Reel L-268)
  - L68-340 to L68-359, 1968 (Reel L-269)
  - L68-360 to L68-383, 1968 (Reel L-270)
  - L68-384 to L68-410, 1968 (Reel L-271)
  - L68-411 to L68-429, 1968 (Reel L-272)
  - L68-430 to L68-451, 1968 (Reel L-273)
  - L68-454 to L68-472, 1968 (Reel L-274)
  - L68-474 to L68-484, 1968 (Reel L-275)
  - L69-2 to L69-24 (continued on reel #L-277), 1969 (Reel L-176)
  - L69-24 to L69-69, 1969 (Reel L-277)
  - L69-71 to L69-103 (continued on reel #L-279), 1969 (Reel L-278)
  - L69-103 to L69-112, 1969 (Reel L-279)
  - L69-113 to L69-149, 1969 (Reel L-280)
  - L69-150 to L69-196 (continued on reel #L-282), 1969 (Reel L-281)
  - L69-196 to L69-204, 1969 (Reel L-282)
  - L69-205 to L69-236, 1969 (Reel L-283)
  - L69-237 to L269, 1969 (Reel L-284)
  - L69-270 to L69-295, 1969 (Reel L-285)
  - L69-297 to L69-311, 1969 (Reel L-286)
  - L69-317 to L69-342, 1969 (Reel L-287)
  - L69-343 to L69-358, 1969 (Reel L-288)
  - L69-360, 1969 (Reel L-289)
  - L69-361 to L69-376, 1969 (Reel L-290)
  - L69-377 to L69-391, 1969 (Reel L-291)
  - L69-389, 1969 (Reel L-292)
  - L69-392 to L69-400, 1969 (Reel L-293)
  - L69-401 to L69-423, 1969 (Reel L-294)
  - L69-424 to L69-444, 1969 (Reel L-295)
  - L69-445 (continued on reel #L-297), 1969 (Reel L-296)
  - L69-445 to L69-465, 1969 (Reel L-297)
  - L69-466 to L69-482, 1969 (Reel L-298)
  - L69-483 to L69-493, 1969 (Reel L-299)
  - L69-494 to L69-509, 1969 (Reel L-300)
  - L69-510 to L69-536, 1969 (Reel L-301)
  - L70-3 to L70-36, 1970 (Reel L-302)
  - L70-38 to L70-81, 1970 (Reel L-303)
  - L70-82 to L70-129 (continued on reel #L-305), 1970 (Reel L-304)
  - L70-129 to L70-157, 1970 (Reel L-305)
  - L70-159 to L70-224, 1970 (Reel L-306)
  - L70-228 to L70-271, 1970 (Reel L-307)
  - L70-273 to L70-276 (continued on reel #L-309), 1970 (Reel L-308)
  - L70-276 to L70-279, 1970 (Reel L-309)
  - L70-283 to L70-336 (continued on reel #L-311), 1970 (Reel L-310)
  - L70-336, 1970 (Reel L-311)
  - L70-337 to L70-382, 1970 (Reel L-312)
  - L70-383 to L70-466, 1970 (Reel L-313)
  - L70-467 to L70-472, 1970 (Reel L-314)
  - L58-571, L59-477, L60-136, L60-1143, L62-1568, L63-404, L64-181, L64-548, L66-267, L66-426, L66-447, L66-525, L67-278, L67-544, L68-104, Multi Year (Reel L-315)
  - L68-161, L68-229, L-68-374, L69-215, 1968-1969 (Reel L-316)
  - L71-1 to L71-26, 1971 (Reel L-317)
  - L71-26 to L71-56, 1971 (Reel L-318)
  - L71-59 to L71-90, 1971 (Reel L-319)
  - L71-91 to L71-139, 1971 (Reel L-320)
  - L71-145 to L71-207, 1971 (Reel L-321)
  - L71-212 to L71-251 (continued on reel #L-323), 1971 (Reel L-322)
  - L71-251 to L71-266, 1971 (Reel L-323)
  - L71-267 to L71-293, 1971 (Reel L-324)
  - L71-294 to L71-325, 1971 (Reel L-325)
  - L71-327 to L71-374, 1971 (Reel L-326)
  - L71-378 to L71-401, 1971 (Reel L-327)
  - L71-405 to L71-410, 1971 (Reel L-328)
  - L72-02 to L72-67 (continued on reel #L-330), 1972 (Reel L-329)
  - L72-67 to L72-91, 1972 (Reel L-330)
  - L72-91 to L72-96 (continued on reel #L-332), 1972 (Reel L-331)
  - L72-96 to L72-124 (continued on reel #L-333), 1972 (Reel L-332)
  - L72-124 to L72-182, 1972 (Reel L-333)
  - L72-183 to L72-236, 1972 (Reel L-334)
  - L72-236 to L72-239 (continued thru reel #L-342), 1972 (Reel L-335)
  - L72-239 (Misc. attachments, A Brainard), 1972 (Reel L-336)
  - L72-329 (Brandeis Univ. Domestic Agriculture policy), 1972 (Reel L-337)
  - L72-239 (Domestic Agriculture policy Harvard Univ.), 1972 (Reel L-338)
  - L72-239 (Harvard Univ. The Military), 1972 (Reel L-339)
  - L72-239 (the Military University of Pennsylvania), 1972 (Reel L-340)
  - L72-239 (University of Pennsylvania University of Virginia), 1972 (Reel L-341)
  - L72-239 (University of Virginia Z) to L72-273, 1972 (Reel L-342)
  - L72-274 to L72-316 (continued on reel #L-344), 1972 (Reel L-343)
  - L72-316 to L72-334(continued on reel #L-345), 1972 (Reel L-344)
  - L72-334 to L72-358 (continued on reel #L-346), 1972 (Reel L-345)
  - L72-358 to L72-410, 1972 (Reel L-346)
  - L72-411 to L72-435, 1972 (Reel L-347)
  - L73-8 to L73-39, 1973 (Reel L-348)
  - L73-42 to L73-86, 1973 (Reel L-349)
  - L73-92 to L73-110 (section 1-16) (continued thru reel #L-352), 1973 (Reel L-350)
  - L73-110 (section 17-56), 1973 (Reel L-351)
  - L73-110 (section 60-end) to L73-116 (continued on reel #L-353), 1973 (Reel L-352)
  - L73-116 to L73-125, 1973 (Reel L-353)
  - L73-126 to L73-167 (continued on reel #L-355), 1973 (Reel L-354)
  - L73-167 to L73-169 (continued on reel #L-356), 1973 (Reel L-355)
  - L73-169 to L73-185, 1973 (Reel L-356)
  - L73-186 to L73-231, 1973 (Reel L-357)
  - L73-237 to L73-275, 1973 (Reel L-358)
  - L73-278 to L73-331 (continued on reel #L-360), 1973 (Reel L-359)
  - L73-331 to L73-386, 1973 (Reel L-360)
  - L73-387 to L73-434 (continued on reel #L-362), 1973 (Reel L-361)
  - L73-434 to L73-455, 1973 (Reel L-362)
  - L57-433, L66-414, L66-322, L66-413, L66-436 (continued on reel #L-364), 1957; 1966 (Reel L-363)
  - L66-436, L66-618, L67-600, L70-232, L70-279, L70-422, L71-413, L72-76, L72-77, L72-135, L72-171, L72-223, L72-249, 1966; 1967; 1970; 1971; 1972 (Reel L-364)
  - L74-7 to L74-29 (continued on reel #L-366), 1974 (Reel L-365)
  - L74-29 to L74-44 (continued thru reel #L-371), 1974 (Reel L-366)
  - L74-44 (Vanderbilt Univ. Indiana Univ.), 1974 (Reel L-367)
  - L74-44 (Indiana Univ. Catholic Univ.), 1974 (Reel L-368)
  - L74-44 (Catholic Univ. Instituto Torcuta D Tella), 1974 (Reel L-369)
  - L74-44 (Institute for Economic Research University College of London), 1974 (Reel L-370)
  - L74-44 (Univ. College of Wales - Z) to L74-49, 1974 (Reel L-371)
  - L74-49 to L74-102, 1974 (Reel L-372)
  - L74-102 to L74-103 (continued thru reel #L-376), 1974 (Reel L-373)
  - L74-103 (Attachments), 1974 (Reel L-374)
  - L74-103 (Attachments cont.), 1974 (Reel L-375)
  - L74-103 (Attachments cont.) to L74-121, 1974 (Reel L-376)
  - L74-123 to L74-154 (continued on reel #L-378), 1974 (Reel L-377)
  - L74-154 to L74-172, 1974 (Reel L-378)
  - L74-225 to L74-261, 1974 (Reel L-379)
  - L74-267, 1974 (Reel L-380)
  - L74-292 to L74-342 (continued on reel #L-382), 1974 (Reel L-381)
  - L74-342 to L74-393 (continued on reel #L-383), 1974 (Reel L-382)
  - L74-393 to L74-412, 1974 (Reel L-383)
  - L75-2 to L75-42, 1975 (Reel L-384)
  - L75-43 to L75-96 (continued on reel #L-386), 1975 (Reel L-385)
  - L75-96 to L75-116 (continued on reel #L-387), 1975 (Reel L-386)
  - L75-116 to L75-136 (continued on reel #L-388), 1975 (Reel L-387)
  - L75-136 to L75-177 (continued on reel #L-389), 1975 (Reel L-388)
  - L75-177 to L75-217 (continued on reel #L-390), 1975 (Reel L-389)
  - L75-217 to L75-231, 1975 (Reel L-390)
  - L75-239 to L75-280, 1975 (Reel L-391)
  - L76-01 to L76-45 (continued on reel #L-393), 1976 (Reel L-392)
  - L76-45 to L76-57 (continued on reel #L-394), 1976 (Reel L-393)
  - L76-57 to L76-89, 1976 (Reel L-394)
  - L76-90 to L76-124 (continued on reel #L-395), 1976 (Reel L-395)
  - L76-124 to L76-174 (continued on reel #L-396), 1976 (Reel L-396)
  - L76-174 to L76-185 (continued on reel #L-397), 1976 (Reel L-397)
  - L76-185 to L76-211 (continued on reel #L-398), 1976 (Reel L-398)
  - L76-211 to L76-301 (L76-284 is included, by missing Start target sheet), 1976 (Reel L-399)
  - L64-553 (A D) (continued on reel #L-401), 1964 (Reel L-400)
  - L64-553 (D Z), 1964 (Reel L-401)
  - L67-238 (continued thru reel #L-404), 1967 (Reel L-402)
  - L67-238, 1967 (Reel L-403)
  - L67-238, L70-247, L71-328, L72-91, L72-106, 1967; 1970; 1971; 1972 (Reel L-404)
  - L64-588, L58-646, L60-136, L63-961, L65-273, 1958; 1960; 1963; 1964; 1965 (Reel L-405)
  - L72-136, L75-90, L75-158, L75-278, 1972; 1975 (Reel L-406)
  - L72-213 to L72-239 (plus Attachments 1-3) (continued thru reel #L409), 1972 (Reel L-407)
  - L72-239 (Attachments 4-12), 1972 (Reel L-408)
  - L72-239 (Attachments 12 End) to L72-306 (continued on reel #L-410), 1972 (Reel L-409)
  - L72-306, L73-49, L73-63, L73-177, L73-351, 1972 (Reel L-410)
  - L74-27, L75-22, L75-191, L75-232, 1974; 1975 (Reel L-411)
  - L71-13, L71-130, L71-212, L71-222, L74-27, 1971; 1974 (Reel L-412)
- 1958
- 1959
- 1960
- 1961
- 1962
  - L62-466: Atlantic College - Grant in aid to establish college, Sir Lawrence Darvall, 1962 (Reel L-170)
    See also Ford Foundation Log file L57-985: Sir Lawrence Darvall - Atlantic Trust for Education of the Free
- 1963
  - L63-835: Consultation on Family Planning Supplies (Submitted by FF New Delhi Field Office), 1963-1968 (Reel L-192)
    Includes correspondence and reports from Ford Foundation Population program staff and Family Planning specialists/consultants in India re: manufacture and procurement of contraceptives, IUDs, and condoms for use in Inida. Includes correspondence with: Dr. Katherine Kuder, Dr. Leona Baumgartner.
    See also Ford Foundation reports #000450, Manufacture of male contraceptives in India, 1964; and 002567, The Nirodh marketing organization, 1964.
    Intrauterine contraceptives -- India; Condoms -- India; Family planning; Family planning services; Population and family planning
- 1964
- 1965
- 1966
- 1967
- 1968
- 1969
- 1970
- 1971
- 1972
- 1973
- 1974
- 1975
- 1976
- 1977
  - L77-1: Ford Foundation: Racial policy issues meeting, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-4: Ford Foundation: Development of communications in developing countries, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-6: Ford Foundation: East-West conferences on European Security, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-11: Ford Foundation: Common problems research competition, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-12: Volunteers in Technical Assistance (V.I.T.A.)(Maryland): General Support, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-16: Ford Foundation: Research Project, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-17: Ford Foundation: Research Project, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-26: Virginia Union University: Program planning and budgeting system, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-27: Ford Foundation: Establishment of a population training institute in Asia, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-29: Commission on the Status of Women (Sacramento, CA): Training activities for local school districts to implement Title IX of the Civil Rights Act, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-34: University of Toronto: Reproductive biology research proposal, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-37: Ford Foundation: Women in Zambia: study of the squatter situation, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-38: Institute for World Order, Inc.: Three proposals, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-39: University of Delaware: The Dalal proposal solar energy demonstration unit for rural development in India, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-41: Center for Urban and Regional Studies (Argentina): Support for urban and regional development research, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-42: Raja Peary Mohan College (India): Research Proposal, 1977 (Reel L-449)
  - L77-42: Raja Peary Mohan College (India): Research Proposal, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-43: Harvard University School of Public Health: Support for research proposal, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-45: Foundation for Management Education (London, England): Teacher fellowships in the U.S., 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-46: Danfarth Foundation (St. Louis, Mo.): Parenting Education Project, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-52: University of California (Berkeley): Support for Center for Continuing Education for Women, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-61: Ford Foundation: Conference on the California Bakke case and affirmative action, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-66: Ford Foundation: Funds for research project, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-72: Ford Foundation: Indonesian Arts and Archaeology, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-75: Radcliffe Institute: Support of a feasibility study for international fellowships, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-83: Ford Foundation: Working group on international economics, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-85: Ford Foundation: Assistance for Kenya's Ministry of Finance and Economic Planning, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-87: U.S. Dept. of Justice (Washington, DC): Communications concerning a program for improvements in the administration of justice, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-88: African American Scholars Council (Washington, DC): Proposal: Change in the role of women in African development planning, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-93: Ford Foundation: Museum training - Asia, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-95: International Fertility Research Program: Research support, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-97: Ford Foundation: Consultants file / Donald H. Graves, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-98: Ford Foundation: Cuban exchange mechanisms, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-99: Ford Foundation: Botswana tribal grazing land programme, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-114: Ford Foundation: Resources and environmental development articles in Pakistani, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-120: Michigan State University: Assessment of school finance reform in Michigan, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-123: Columbia University: Agriculture Network, 1977 (Reel L-465)
  - L77-127: Ford Foundation: West Africa - Health Education, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-128: Brookings Institution: Proposal U.S. policy toward South Africa, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-129: Ford Foundation: Algerian situation, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-134: Bangladesh Krishi (Agricultural) Bank: Rural Credit, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-135: Ford Foundation: OLAC representative's meeting in Brazil, October, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-136: 42nd Street Local Development (NYC): Loan to complete financing of a theatre complex, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-144: Zero Population Growth (Washington, DC): Population Education Project, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-145: Ford Foundation: Maize and wheat program - Egypt, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-148: Gonoshasthya Kendra: Support for the People's Heath Center, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-149: Prajna Pathashala Mandal: Fund raising drive for expanding Mandal staff, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-150: National Foundation for Research on Human Resource Development: To establish a foundation, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-153: Ford Foundation: Funds for individual award, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-154: Ford Foundation: Survey of reproductive sciences in India, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-158: Carnegie Mellon University: Funds for program to train black Rhodesians in public management, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-160: Kuwait University: Development of graduate studies at the university, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-164: Ford Foundation: Urban Universities, 1977 (Reel L-420)
  - L77-164: Ford Foundation: Urban Universities, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-165: California Community Colleges (Sacramento, Calif): Community College Finance Project, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-166: Ford Foundation: Agricultural Administration, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-168: U.N. Development Program: A program for research and training in Trypanosomia, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-170: Ford Foundation: Information log on Southern Africa, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-171: The Pennsylvania State University: Research proposal on rural-urban migration and economic development, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-172: American Association of Community and Junior College (Washington, DC): International Education Program, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-175: Ford Foundation: Nigerian Language Symposium Oct-Nov., 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-177: Indian Institute of World economics: Provide for research in the area of international economics, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-178: International Federation for Family Promotion (Quebec, Canada): An Information log, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-179: Ford Foundation: Additional support for university centers in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-181: Ford Foundation: Support for Chong-Sik Lee, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-187: Ford Foundation: Support on U.S.-Latin American relations, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-188: C.L.A.C.S.O. (Latin American Council of Social Sciences) (Argentina): Support for working seminar on higher education, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-189: University of the West Indies (Regional Pre-school Child Development Centre): Research in child development, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-190: Yale University: Evaluation of Push/Excel project (see PA78-304), 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-191: Brookings Institution: Proposal on international economic policy, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-192: Yale University: Research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-193: Columbia University: Research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-421)
  - L77-193: Columbia University: Research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-194: The University of Sussex: Research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-195: Johns Hopkins University: Research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-196: Tufts University (MASS): Research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-200: University of Michigan: Linkages re: International dimension of continuing research education in social sciences, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-201: California University of Berkeley: Research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-202: Ford Foundation: School desegregation, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-203: New York Shakespeare Festival: A loan to finance rehabilitation of the Delacorte Theatre in Central Park, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-205: Tufts University (MASS): Support of research on Haitian migration to be conducted in collaboration with the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-208: North Carolina, University of Chapel Hill: Proposal for research training center in International security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-210: Ford Foundation: OLAC Social Science Meeting, 1978, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-211: University Illinois at Urbana: Proposal for research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-422)
  - L77-211: University Illinois at Urbana: Proposal for research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-211: University Illinois at Urbana: Proposal for research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-447)
  - L77-214: National Center for Higher Education Management Systems, Boulder, Colorado: Assess the quality of graduate education and research programs in major research universities, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-219: Ford Foundation: East European foreign affairs specialists, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-220: Massachusetts Institute of Technology: M.I.T./Cairo University technological planning program, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-222: Ford Foundation: Spanish Brookings, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-226: Ford Foundation: Soviet migr Artists, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-230: University of Denver: Science Technology and Development in the Middle East, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-231: University of the Witwatersrand (S.Africa): To establish a center for applied legal studies, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-233: Georgetown University: Research and training center in international security and arms control, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-236: Ford Foundation: Development of social science research policy analysis in Egypt, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-237: American University of Beirut: Exchange of professors faculties of agriculture, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-241: Bank of Thailand: Commodity conference, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-242: South African Medical Scholarship Trusts, Cape town, South Africa: Student research fund for black students, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-249: Ford Foundation: Middle East Film Festival, 1977 (Reel L-423)
  - L77-250: Ford Foundation: Funds for proposals a) labor law teaching and curriculum programs b) West coast research institute on South Africa, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-258: University of Kentucky, Appalachian Center: Proposal for a Kentucky school finance reform project, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-259: American Council on Education, Washington, DC: Higher education program in Southern Africa, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-260: Harvard University, Boston, Mass: Proposal Labor Market Behavior in Developing Nations, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-261: Middle East Institute, Washington, DC: Funds for a special studies program, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-262: Ford Foundation: Support for proposal on the effect of Soviet American exchanges on civic consciousness in Russia, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-263: Ford Foundation: Proposal on food policy, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-267: Hartman Theatre, Stanford, Conn.: Support of Hartman Theatre, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-268: Ford Foundation: General information log on migration, 1977 (Reel L-448)
  - L77-269: Ford Foundation: General information on world debt problems, 1977 (Reel L-448)
- 1978
  - L78-7: Brookings Institution: Two proposals on peace in the Middle East, 1978 (Reel L-436)
  - L78-8: Ford Foundation: Environmental development concern in Tunisia, 1978 (Reel L-436)
  - L78-13: Ford Foundation: Background papers on Middle East conference, 1978 (Reel L-436)
  - L78-14: University of Pennsylvania: Proposal on functional courses in Arabic for Business, 1978 (Reel L-436)
  - L78-15: The Pennsylvania State University: Information Log, 1978 (Reel L-436)